MAN 1 ON COMPUTER: Mistress,
spank my bottom. Spank it really hard!
Please, spank my bottom!
엉덩이를 때려 주세요!
- That is unpleasant.
- Spank it really hard.
이건 좀 아닌데
더 세게!
WOMAN ON COMPUTER: Lick my nipples.
내 젖꼭지를 핥아
No, thank you, pregnant lady.
사양할게요
임신한 아주머니
MAN 2 ON COMPUTER: Strip, soldier!
제군들이여 벗어라!
You're gonna find out
why they call me the drill sergeant.
내가 왜 드릴 하사관인지 보여주지
(WHIP CRACKS)
번역- robholic
수정 금지
(SIGHS)
번역- robholic
수정 금지
That's... That's nice, baby.
번역- robholic
수정 금지
No, Frizzy! No!
안 돼, 프리지! 안돼
(GROANING)
(GASPING)
No, no, no, Frizzy! No!
하지마, 안돼 프리지! 안돼~
Frizzy.
프리지
(PHONE BEEPS)
No, no, no, wait! Cody! No.
안돼, 기다려!
코디 안돼
번
번역
번역-
번역- r
번역- ro
번역- rob
번역- robh
번역- robho
번역- robhol
번역- robholi
번역- robholic
수
수정
번역- robholic
수정 금
수정 금지
ROB ON PHONE: No, no, no, Frizzy! No!
하지마, 안돼 프리지! 안돼~
Don't worry about it, man.
Everyone's got a sex tape.
걱정마, 짜샤
모두 섹스 테이프 정돈 가지고 있어
Please.
제발
Yeah, except they're having sex with people.
그래
다른 사람들은 사람이랑 섹스한다는 게 다르지
- (GRO ANING) Frizzy.
- Right.
프리지
It's not technically incest
if your family member's a different species.
너희 가족 중 하나가 다른 종이라면
그래도 근친은 아냐
So, are you getting close with Dana yet?
근데 너 다나랑 좀 잘 되고 있냐?
The rumours are true.
She's taken the pledge.
루머가 사실이었어
다나가 서약을 했대
No sex? She was your sure thing.
섹스를 안한다고?
너랑 당연히 할 줄 알았는데
- Faith-camp propaganda, man.
- NATHAN: She's waiting until marriage.
순결 캠프는 다 구라야
다나는 결혼할 때까지 기다리고 싶대
I thought she had sex with six guys.
난 걔가 벌써 6명이랑
한 줄 알았는데
What?
왜요?
Get to class.
교실로 들어가라
No cell phones in the hall, Alyson.
앨리슨 복도에서 핸드폰 쓰지 마라
You can pick this up from my office
today after school.
이따가 수업 끝나고 내 사무실로
와서 찾아가도록 해라
No, no, no, Frizzy! No! Frizzy!
하지마, 안돼 프리지! 안돼~
Well, I've seen worse.
이보다 더한 것도 봤는데 뭘
No, no, no, Frizzy! No!
하지마, 안돼 프리지! 안돼~
(CLEARS THROAT)
Miss Johnson. Lunch today?
존슨 선생님
같이 점심 먹을 까요?
I'll have to check my calendar, perv...Pete.
제 스케쥴 좀 확인 하구요
변(pervert: 변태).. 아니 피트
No, no, no, Frizzy! No! Frizzy!
하지마, 안돼 프리지! 안돼~
Look. Look. Look at that.
이 것 좀 봐
No, no, no, Frizzy! No! Frizzy!
하지마, 안돼 프리지! 안돼~
(CHEERLEADER EXCLAIMS IN DISGUST)
- Hey, just ignore them.
- Oh, God. You saw it, too?
그냥 무시해
오 세상에
너도 봤어?
- Just so you know, it's not at all...
- Hey, don't worry about it.
사실 그건 말야
알아 걱정마
Frizzy's a good-looking dog.
프리지 정말 잘생긴 개던데
So, do you wanna
do it? Are we on?
그럼 너 할거야?
Rob? Rob? Are we on for seventh period?
롭? 롭?
우리 7교시에 보는 거지?
Yeah. l...I'll...
응
- I'll meet you over there.
- Okay.
그래 이따 봐
알았어
- Doggy style!
- Hey, Stifler.
강아지 스타일!
안녕 스티플러
Is that your girlfriend?
네 여친이야?
No, we're just...We're just...
We're friends.
아니 우린 그냥 친구야
Just friends? How sweet.
그냥 친구?
좋기도 하겠다
Well, she seems awful ripe.
If you don't pick the fruit, I will.
쟤 정말 죽이는데
네가 안 가지면 내가 가진다
STIFLER: Hey, beautiful.
안녕, 이쁜이
STIFLER: Wow!
와우
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
CHARLES ON PA: Good morning,
East Great Falls Blazers.
이스트 그레이트 폴스 학생 여러분
좋은 아침입니다
Don't forget about the big game
against Central this week
이번주에 센트럴과의
큰 경기 잊지 마세요
and the Aloha Dance this Friday
from 7:00 to midnight.
그리고 알로하 댄스파티가 금요일
저녁 7시부터 자정까지 있을 예정입니다
Hawaiian shirts and leis
are recommended for entrance.
하와이안 셔츠나 꽃 목걸이
착용하는 거 잊지 마세요
(CHARLES GIGGLES)
- PRINCIPAL ON PA: Charles, knock that off.
- Sorry.
찰스 그만 해라
죄송해요
(MR O'DONNELL CLEARS THROAT)
Let's focus on the quiz, please.
퀴즈에 집중 좀 하자
Douche bag.
병신
I'm serious about this pledge, you know.
난 이 서약 진지하게 생각해
I know.
알아
- So just dancing tonight.
- Yeah. Just dancing.
-그냥 춤만 추는거다
-그래 그냥 춤만
The horizontal hula.
훌라춤(horizontal hula) !
hotizontal dancing(성교)을 이용한 말 장난
Nathan.
네이슨
Poor Nathan.
불쌍한 네이슨
His willy must be hard enough
to cut glass by now.
지금쯤이면 똘똘이가 딱딱해서
유리를 자를 정도일텐데
Nathan loves me, and Nathan respects me.
그래
A. 여자를 존중한다고 해서 남자는
섹스를 포기하지는 않아
Okay. A, a guy never respects a girl
enough to give up sex.
그리고 B
넌 어때?
And, B, well, what about you?
다나 너 지금쯤이면
매우 달아 올랐을텐데
You must be feeling
pretty randy by now, Dana.
맞아, 사실 조금
Okay, well, yeah, maybe, like,
the tiniest bit,
하지만 난 정말 뭔가 더 높은
힘으로 연결된 거 같은 느낌이 들어
but I really feel like I'm connecting
with the higher power here.
그래, 그게 매우 멋진 건 알지만
Yes, I know, and that is totally fab,
난 못 하겠어
내가 너무 입으로 하는 걸
좋아해서 말야
but I know I couldn't do it.
I'm way too into giving blow jobs.
리차드한테 물어봐
Ask Richard.
이모진 말 듣지마
(이모진은 셰익스피어 작품에 나오는
정조있는 여주인공)
Hey, don't listen to lmogen, okay?
섹스는 정말 중요해
그리고 네가 준비가 안 된 거 같으면
Sex is a really big deal,
and if you feel like you're not ready,
기다리는 게 좋을 거야
then I think you should wait.
하지만
DANA: But...
미안하지만 하이디
넌 도대체 네가 무슨 말
하는지 알기나 하니?
No offence, Heidi, but you have no idea
what you're talking about.
나중에 문자해
Text me later.
안녕, 롭
응?
- Hey, Rob.
- ROB: Yeah?
뭐 좀 물어봐도 돼?
물론, 뭔데?
- Can I ask you something?
- Sure. What's up?
이거 좀 사적인데
Well, it's kind of personal.
응
Okay.
내가 생각해 본 건데
너 내가 처녀인 거 알지?
I've been thinking.
You know I'm a virgin, right?
그냥... 나도 모르겠어
It's just...I don't know.
모두 다 옛날 옛 적에
다 해버린 거 같아
Everyone's already done it
like a million times already,
그리고 난 남친 비슷한 거도 없고
and I know I don't have a boyfriend
or whatever, but...
하지만 가끔 난 그냥
잊어 버려야 할 거 같아
But sometimes I feel like I should just
get it over with.
그러니까 내 말은 이 것도
지날갈 일이잖아
처녀라는 거
You know? I mean,
just get past this whole thing, this virgin.
이게 도대체 무슨 의미가 있겠어?
What does that even mean, anyway?
내가 한 번도 해본 적이 없는데
그래서 그게 뭐?
So I've never had a penis in my vagina,
but so what?
Why do I have to label everything?
Like, "She's too innocent.
"She can't handle it:"
I'm not that innocent.
"쟤는 못 할 거야"
난 그렇게 순진하지 않아
I've seen Showgirls and Blue Lagoon.
나도 쇼걸이랑 블루 라군 봤다고
(둘 다 야한 영화 제목)
Anyways, I think I've decided to just do it.
But what do you think?
어쨌든, 나 그냥 하기로 했어
어떻게 생각해?
Yeah. I think you should definitely
go ahead and get it over with.
그래 그러는 게 좋을 거 같아
(LAUGHS) Thanks.
고마워
Let's get back to work.
이제 공부하러 가야겠다
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
(WHOOPS)
Stifcam coming at you live
from the Aloha Dance
이스트 그레이트 폴스
알로하 댄스파티에서
here at the East Great Falls...
스티프 캠을 생방송으로
진행하고 있습니다
This chick just grabbed my ass.
아가씨가 방금
제 엉덩이를 잡았는데
She wants to play
the Stifmeister's flute skin.
제 똘똘이와 놀고
싶은가 보네요
Let go find some of that
sweet-looking pinoche, Gibbsy.
깁스비 가서 이쁜이들
좀 찾아 보자
Hey, check it out.
There's Heidi.
야, 저기 하이디다
LUBE: All right, all right.
She looks highly doable.
좋아, 정말 예쁜데
All right, so what's the game plan here?
그래, 오늘의 계획은 뭐야?
I don't know. Ask
her to dance, I guess.
몰라, 그냥 가서
춤추자고 하는 거?
You need a plan, all right?
It's all about establishing your intentions.
계획이 있어야 해
우리가 목적을
달성하려면 말이지
See, right now,
she thinks of you as just a friend.
쟤는 아직 널 친구로
생각하고 있잖아
You need to break that paradigm.
넌 그 생각을 타파할
필요가 있어
Remember, friends don't let friends
just be friends.
기억해, 친구는 절대 친구가
그냥 친구가 되도록
내버려 두지 않아
- Right.
- I'm serious. You cannot puss out here.
맞아
넌 여기서 물러날 수 없어
All right, take it easy.
I'm gonna go talk to her.
알았어, 진정해
가서 얘기해 볼게
Wait. Aren't you forgetting something?
잠깐, 너 뭐 잊지 않았어?
Oh. Oh. Oh.
오
Here, don't forget these.
여어, 잊지마
You only need those when you're alone.
너 실패하면 이 거 써야겠다
Right. Right. Okay.
알았어, 가 봐
- (EXCLAIMS) Okay!
- What? What's wrong?
그만!
왜 무슨 일이야?
I can't.
난 못 해
- But it's only second base.
- I know. But if we go there,
그냥 2단계잖아
나도 알아, 하지만 우리가
then we're gonna wanna go further.
2단계를 넘어가면
더 가고 싶을 거 아냐
But Adam and Eve did it.
아담과 이브도 그랬어
(GASPS)
I'm sorry. Hey, hey.
미안해
I love you. Do you know that?
난 널 사랑해, 알지?
Come here.
이리 와
Is God okay with a blow job?
입으로 해도
괜찮겠지?
(GASPS)
I thought you understood
how I felt about this.
네가 날 이해하는 줄 알았어
I told you, it's important for me
to save myself until marriage.
내가 중요하다고 했잖아
You've had sex with seven guys.
너 이미 7명이랑 했잖아
(GASPING)
And it was six, not seven!
7명이 아니라 6명이라고!
Well, one was a black guy,
so he counts as two.
한 명은 흑인이었으니깐
2명으로 쳐야겠네
Dana.
다나
- Dana, come on.
- Fuck off.
다나, 그러지 마
엿 먹어
Dana. Come on, Dana. Dana!
다나, 가지마
다나!
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey, girls.
This is gonna be for Sit-on-my-face-book.
안녕, 이쁜이들
내 페이스북에 올릴 건데 말야
I need you to kiss one time, okay?
둘이 한 번 같이 키스 좀 해 줘
I don't know.
싫은데
Come on.
It's gonna be seen by millions of people.
왜~
수 많은 사람들이 볼 텐데
(LAUGHS) Okay.
알았어
(BOYS CHEERING)
Okay, we're gonna go again,
좋았어, 한 번 더 찍을 건데
but this time,
sneak in some tongue for daddy.
이번에는 날 위해
혀도 좀 넣어 봐
Okay.
좋아
(LAUGHS EXCITEDLY)
(HIGH-PITCHED VOICE)
That's what I'm talking about, baby!
그래 그거야!
(BOYS CHEERING)
Stifmeister strikes again!
스티플러님이 또 한 건 해냈습니다!
Dude.
야
You're gonna love this.
Check this out.
이 거 봐
Yeah. So?
그래서?
Watch and learn.
잘 보고 배우라고
"You're hot.
넌 정말 섹시해
"Give me your number
and let's get together:"
번호 좀 줘
우리 같이 놀자
I throw this at a hot girl,
내가 이 걸 예쁜 애한테 주면
and she's so impressed
that I'm literally throwing around a Benjamin
걔가 감동 받을 거야
말 그대로 100달러니까
that she wants to hook up with me.
그리고 나와 섹스하고
싶어 하겠지
Yeah. Good luck with that.
그래 잘 해 봐라
- I'm gonna go find Dana.
- All right, man.
난 다나 찾으러 갈게
알았어
Oh, no.
안 돼
Oh, God.
세상에
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Watch out. Coming through.
실례해요
지나갈게요
(DANCE SONG PLAYING)
So, I was thinking about what
we were talking about, you know, before.
저기 우리가 저번에 얘기한 거 말야
- Yeah. Yeah, I remember.
- Right. So I was thinking, why wait?
응 기억나
왜 안 되겠어?
Right? I mean, you might as well,
you know, get it over with.
그치? 내 말은 하는거 말야
What? Like, here? At the dance?
뭐? 여기서?
댄스 파티에서?
Well, there's always the library.
도서관도 있잖아
- Yeah, the library.
- I'm kidding.
그래, 도서관
농담이야
- Yeah. I know.
- But seriously, after the dance,
그래 알아
사실은 파티 끝나고
I don't know if you...
너 혹시
- What are you doing?
- Looking for my money.
뭐 해?
돈 찾고 있어
- C-note thing?
- Yeah.
100달러?
응
- Lose your money?
- Shut up.
돈을 잃어 버렸다고?
닥쳐
Ooh.
오
And we're back. What's up, dude?
Where's Heidi?
무슨 일이야?
하이디 어딨어?
I don't know.
나도 몰라
- She was here a second ago.
- Maybe she went to the bathroom.
아까 여기 있었는데
화장실 갔나 보지
- Yeah, maybe.
- Dana's pissed at me.
그런가 봐
다나가 나한테 화났어
Dude, you gotta play along
with this whole pledge thing.
너 그 서약 따위 때문에 그러는 거야?
Well, that's easy for you to say.
말이야 쉽지
You haven't exactly
broken the seal yet, either.
너 아직 봉인 해제도 못 했잖아
Dude, I've been getting to third base
on a regular basis.
나 막 3단계로 가던
참이었다고
I can't go back to jacking off now.
나 다시 자위할 순 없어
Dude, just use your left hand.
It feels completely different.
그냥 왼 손 쓰는 게 어때?
느낌이 완전 달라
- I'm gonna go find Heidi.
- I'm gonna go find Dana.
난 하이디 찾으러 간다
난 다나 찾으러 갈래
야 너 때문에
토할 거 같잖아
BOY: (LAUGHS) No! Dude,
you're gonna make me hurl.
Heidi?
하이디?
안 돼
LUBE: No, no, no, no!
잠깐
Wait.
이봐
Dude, yo.
What are you doing?
Rob? You said...
롭? 네가...
Rob!
롭!
(EXCLAIMS)
Dude, nice cock block.
야, 멋진데
(SHRIEKS)
I'm on fire.
나한테 불 붙었어
- I'm on fire.
- Oh, my God.
불 붙었다고
오 세상에
There's a fire. There's a fire,
and it's on me.
불이다
내가 끌게
Oh, my God.
오 맙소사
HEIDl: Rob! Rob! Put it out. Take off
your pants! Take off...Take your pants off!
롭! 롭 바지 벗어
빨리 바지 벗어
Oh, God!
어떡해
(SHRIEKS) Come on!
빨리 와!
(SHRIEKS)
Oh, my God. Oh,
my God! Oh, my God!
오 세상에
어떡해 어떡해
Hurry, Rob, come on.
빨리, 롭
빨리
Get it out! Get it out!
어서 꺼내!
(FIRE ALARM RINGING)
(SHRIEKS)
Oh, God.
맙소사
What the hell is going on in here?
도대체 무슨 일이야?
Two months seems like an awfully long time
for Saturday detention.
2달 동안 토요일마다 벌 받는 건
좀 긴 거 같은데
We're supposed to clean up the library.
도서관 청소해서 그래요
Do you guys know where the vacuum is?
진공 청소기 봤니?
Nope.
아뇨
What were you doing in the library anyway?
도대체 도서관은
왜 간 거니?
I wasn't doing anything.
Heidi was already in there.
아무 것도 안 했어요
하이디가 거기 있길래
- I was just looking for her.
- I heard she was blowing some dude.
하이디를 찾으러 다녔거든요
나는 누굴 입으로 해 주고
있었다고 들었는데
Cody! Well, I don't know
how you're gonna go on the school ski trip
코디!
네가 계속 벌 받는 중이면
if you're still on detention.
학교 스키 캠프에 갈 수
있을지 모르겠구나
Mom, I don't see what that has to do with it.
I didn't do anything.
엄마 전 진짜
아무 짓도 안 했어요
I heard you were the fluffer.
형이 '플러퍼' 였다며
(fluffer란 포르노에서 남자 배우의 성기가
발기된 상태로 유지되도록 하는 여자)
- Cody.
- Look. His lips are chapped.
코디
보세요 형 입술이 텄잖아요
(EXCLAIMS)
Well, we'll see.
생각 해 볼 게
All right. I have to go get ready.
알았어요
저 나갈 준비 할 게요
Maybe it's in the garage.
창고에 있는 거 같구나
Rob? I wanna have
a little chat with you.
롭?
너랑 얘기 좀 했으면 하는데
Do we have to?
꼭이요?
Honey, I know that you're growing older,
아가야 나도 네가
나이든 걸 알지만
and I don't know what your father
has told you about things,
너희 아버지가 말해 줬는지
모르겠구나
but I think it's important to discuss
everything, you know?
내 생각엔 모든 걸 얘기하는 게
좋은 거 같구나
Like about sex.
섹스 말이다
- Are you having sex?
- Mom, I don't wanna talk about this.
내가 세탁소에서
양말을 찾아 왔는데
No, well, it's just that I found
this sock in the laundry, and, well...
오 세상에
엄마 저리 치워요
Oh, God, Mom. Put that away.
그리고 누가 나한테
비디오를 보냈더구나
And, also,
somebody sent me a link to this video.
하지마, 안돼 프리지! 안돼~
ROB: No, no, no, Frizzy! No.
-엄마 꺼요!
-어떻게 하는지 몰라!
- Mom, just turn it off!
- I don't know how!
네 동생이 배경 화면으로
해 놨단 말야
Your brother made it my start-up screen.
-제가 바꿀 게요
-정말?
- Okay, I can...I can fix that.
- You can? Great.
네
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
하지마, 안돼 프리지! 안돼~
얘기 나눠서 좋았구요
- No, no, no, Frizzy! No!
- Thank you for that.
자 이제 됐죠?
그쵸?
- Okay.
- And we're done. Right? Yeah.
아가야
부끄러울 필요 없단다
Well, honey, please.
There's no reason to be ashamed.
자위는 자연스러운 거야
Masturbation is perfectly natural.
내 말은 네 나이 또래 애들 중에는
이미 해 본 애들도 있겠지만
I mean, boys your age
are maybe into experimentation
동물이랑 하는 것도 말이다
and trying new things with animals.
프리지는 아기 강아지 때 부터
우리랑 함께 지냈잖니
I mean, Frizzy, she's been in our family for...
Since she was a puppy...
저 늦었어요
(STAMMERS) Hey, I'm late.
-늦었구나
-죄송해요
- You're tardy.
- Sorry.
손상된 책들
치우는 것 부터 해라
You can start by cleaning off
all the damaged books
그리고 망가진 거 분류하고
내가 지켜보마
and separating the ruined ones.
I'll be checking on you.
하이디, 어제 말야
Heidi. Look, about last night...
별로 얘기하고 싶지 않아
I don't wanna talk about it.
-난 그냥
-롭
- Well, I just wanted to tell you...
- Rob.
이 것 좀 비우고 올게
I'm gonna go empty this bucket.
내가 뭘 찾았는지 알아?
Do you have any
idea what I found here?
이 건 성경이야!
난 이게 전설인 줄만 알았는데
- This is the bible.
- I thought that was an urban legend.
아냐 이건 진짜야
거의 몇 십년이나 된 거라고
No. This is real.
This goes back decades.
그래, 그래서?
Okay. So what?
이게 바로 우리에게
필요한 거야
This is exactly what we need
to finally get laid.
이 게 뭘 도와준다는 건데?
다 탔구만
How is this thing gonna help us get laid?
It's ruined.
거의 읽지도
못 하겠다
You can't even read most of it.
이 책은 학교에서 매년 행운의
사나이 한 명을 도와줬었어
This book has helped one lucky guy
each year at Great Falls.
그리고 올해는
그 사나이가 바로 나야
And this year, that lucky guy is us.
좀 탔지만 그래도 여전히 좋은
정보가 있어 이 것 봐봐
Even with the damage, it still has
a ton of useful stuff. Check this out.
1977년 2월 1일
G-스팟
"February 1st, 1977.
The G-spot:"
그 정돈 아는데
또 뭐 있어?
- I can dig it.
- LUBE: What else you got?
1991년
어떻게 털을 깎아야
똘똘이가 더 커보이는가
"1991 . How to shave your pubes
to make your dick look bigger:"
아빠가 보여준 적 있어
Dad showed me that one.
2003년 방금 경험한
놀라운 성경험
"2003. I just had
the most amazing sexual experience:"
여기 잘 안 보이는 게 있는데
"그녀는 박하사탕을 사용했다"
Something I can't read.
"She used a breath mint:"
박하 사탕?
뭐하러?
A breath mint? For what?
야 이 멍청아
박하 사탕을 똥꼬에 넣으면 사탕 때문에
똥꼬가 꽉 쪼여질 거 아냐
You moron. You stick it up your tailpipe and
the minty-ness makes your asshole twitch.
Everyone knows that.
모두 다 알던데
Dude, I don't know.
This sounds pretty weak.
야, 난 모르겠다
이 거 좀 이상해
Plus, I mean, we can find most of this stuff
on the internet anyway.
게다가 이런 거
인터넷에 널렸잖아
No, this is different.
This has personal experiences.
이 건 달라
개인적인 경험들이잖아
Plus, it's custom-tailored to
Great Falls girls.
게다가 우리 학교 여자애들의
취향에 따라 수정되기도 한 거고
Since when does punani have a zip code?
언제부터 여자의 거기마다
서로 다른 취향이 있었다고
What have we got to lose? Nathan,
you've been working on Dana for, what?
우리가 잃을 게 뭐 있어?
다나한테 네가 왜 작업한건데?
Like six months? Only to find out that
she loves the Lord more than sex?
6달 동안이나 다나가 섹스보다 신을
더 좋아한다는 걸 알려고?
And, Lube, how have all your schemes
to get laid been working out so far?
루브 넌 네 계획마다
제대로 되는 게 없잖아
Minus $100.
100달러 잃었지
Exactly, and me, well, I've been wasting
all my time on some fantasy that someday
그래 그러니까!
난 내 삶을 언젠가는
하이디가 날 사랑할거라는
Heidi's gonna fall madly in love with me.
Face it, guys, we need help.
환상으로 낭비하고 있었어
And this is it, staring
us right in the face.
그리고 이 게 바로 우릴
바른 길로 인도해 줄거야
- I'm in.
- All right.
나 낄래
좋아
I'm in.
나도
- Yeah.
- Yes.
좋아
(ALL WHOOPING)
- Yeah!
좋아!
Hey, easy. Guys, it's old.
야 조심해
이 거 골동품이야
"May 1st, 1990.
1990년 5월 1일
"The simplest way into a girl's pants
is still basic flattery:"
여자와 자기 위한
기본은 바로 아부다
That's it? Just flatter her?
그게 다야?
그냥 아부하라고?
- That's it.
- Well, think about it.
그래 이 거야
잘 생각해 봐
How many times do you actually do it?
너 얼마나 아부해봤냐?
Walk up to a girl and say,
"Wow, you have beautiful eyes:"
여자애한테 가서
"와~ 넌 정말 눈이 예뻐"
Like, never. It's telling us the only proven
way to get women is to be an asshole,
절대 안하지
내 말은 여자를 얻기 위해서는
나쁜 남자가 되야 해
'cause the guys that actually spew
that kind of crap get laid.
왜냐면 아부하는 사람은
여자랑 자려고 그러는 거니까
Check it out. Twelve o'clock.
12시 방향 주목
(NATHAN EXCLAIMS)
(CHATTERING)
(WHISTLES)
- All right. Let's put this bible to a test.
- Yes.
그래, 자 시험해 보자
좋아
- You go talk to her.
- I'm not trying it out on Ashley.
네가 가서 말해 봐
난 애슐리한테는 안 할래
Why don't you go talk to her,
'cause you're the one who likes her?
네가 가서 말하는 게 어때?
너 애슐리 좋아하잖아
- I'm eating.
- Okay. I'll do it.
나 지금 먹고 있잖아
알았어 내가 할게
Hey, Ashley.
안녕 애슐리
Hey, Rob. Shopping for your girlfriend?
안녕 롭
네 여친 줄 거 사니?
No...This is...
It's for my mom.
아니, 이 건 엄마 꺼야
She's dating again.
요즘 데이트 하셔서
(NERVOUS LAUGH)
Well, you know, l...
Actually, I wanted to say,
사실은 말야 너한테
you know,
you have the most gorgeous teeth.
네 치아가 정말 멋진다는 걸
말하고 싶었어
Hey. Come with me.
나랑 같이 가자
Jealous? He's making a move
on your lady friend.
질투나?
네 여자랑 가고 있는데
Unlike you, I don't mind sharing my women.
너랑 달리 난 내 여자를
나누는 데 인색하지 않아
(LAUGHS) And what are
you wankers up to today?
자위쟁이들이
여긴 웬 일이야?
- (IN BRITISH ACCENT) Cheerio.
- (IN BRITISH ACCENT) Hello, love.
안녕
안녕 이쁜이
Word to your mumsie.
너희 어머니께
안부 전해 드려
Just waiting for some ladies
to join us, in fact.
우리랑 같이 놀 아가씨들을
기다리고 있었어
You nancy boys couldn't get laid
at a Jonas Brothers concert
게이 귀염둥이들
너흰 조나스 브라더스 콘서트의
with a fistful of backstage passes. Cheerio.
대기실 입장권이 많아도
여자랑 잘 수 없을 걸, 안녕
(IN NORMAL ACCENT)
Was that a slam?
우리를 놀린거지?
(IN NORMAL ACCENT)
You bet your bollocks.
당연하지
- Hold this.
- Yeah.
이 것 좀 들어 줘
그래
How does this look?
어때?
Great, I'll take it.
좋아, 이 걸로 해야지
Stand up.
일어나
Wait, what...What's...Wait, hold...Hold on.
잠깐 잠깐
뭐야
Oh.
오
(GROANS)
(GASPING)
Should I call you?
너한테 전화해야 해?
Just walk out of the store
and meet me at the food court.
그냥 가게 나가서
나랑 푸드코트에서 만나
Act natural.
자연스럽게 행동해
(INAUDIBLE)
Can I help you?
무엇을 도와드릴까요?
No. No. I'm...I'm just browsing.
아뇨
그냥 구경 중이에요
Okay, then.
알겠습니다
- Have a nice day.
- You, too.
좋은 하루 되세요
아줌마도요
(ALARM SOUNDING)
I'm sorry! I wasn't stealing.
It was a...It was a prank.
죄송해요, 제가 안 훔쳤어요
장난이에요
I am so sorry.
I think we left the tags on your garments.
죄송합니다
속옷에서 가격표를
안 떼었나보네요
Please come back to the register.
We'll figure this out. I'm so embarrassed.
계산대로 다시 와주세요
제가 해결해 드리겠습니다
Oh, my God.
오 세상에
Sorry, l...I got excited.
죄송해요
전 그냥 흥분되어서
(CLEARS THROAT)
(WHISPERS)
That'll be 149.90.
149.90 달러입니다
- How much?
- 149.90.
얼마라구요?
140.90 달러요
But they're so small.
정말 작은데
- Madeleine?
- It's my mom. I'm...I have a note.
매들린?
엄마예요, 저 수표있어요
(LAUGHS)
- Thank you.
- Have a nice day.
감사합니다
좋은 하루 되세요
Come again.
또 오세요
What took you so long?
Did you get it?
왜 이렇게 오래 걸렸어?
가져 왔어?
Sure did. I even stole you a bag so
you don't have to touch it till you get home.
물론이지
담아 가라고 쇼핑백도 훔쳐왔어
Great. Thanks.
고마워
Hey. What's up, Ashley?
안녕, 애슐리?
What are you pillow biters doing here?
너네 여기서 뭐하냐?
Stifler.
스티플러
Don't eat that.
You're gonna get fat.
먹지마
살찔 거야
I'm super horny.
Wanna suck me off in the Sharper lmage?
나 지금 미치겠는데
내 꺼 빨아 주고 더 날씬해 질래?
Okay.
좋아
(GIGGLING)
(CHURCH ORGAN PLAYING)
(WHISPERING) Dana.
Excuse me. I'm so sorry.
다나
실례할게요, 죄송합니다
Didn't mean to disrupt the...
This morning's mass.
일부러 망치려고 한 거 아냐
(WHISPERING) What are you doing here?
여기서 뭐 하는 거야?
I wanted to say I'm sorry.
미안하다고 말하고 싶어서
Did you really think that
this is the best time to discuss this?
지금이 말하기 적절한
시간이라고 생각한 거야?
Well, you weren't answering any of my texts.
내 문자에 답장을 안 하길래
(SHUSHING)
- I'll be right back, okay?
- (WHISPERING) Okay.
잠깐 나갔다 올게요
그래
PRIEST ON PA: What is faith?
믿음이 무엇입니까?
When you flip the light switch
in your kitchen,
부엌의 불을 킬 때
you know that the light will turn on.
당신은 불이
켜지리라는 것을 압니다
Some might call that faith, but I tell you,
that is not the real faith.
누군가는 그 걸 믿음이라 하겠지만
전 그 것이 진짜 믿음이 아니라 생각합니다
Okay, so what is so important that
you needed to come and interrupt church?
도대체 뭐가 그리 중요해서
교회까지 와서 날 방해하는 거야?
I don't really get why
you're so mad at me right now.
네가 나한테 왜 그리
화났는지 모르겠어
Because you don't respect me.
This is all just a big joke to you.
왜냐면 넌 날 존중하지 않잖아
내 말이 농담으로 들리니?
You know what? You're right,
because this is just another phase for you.
그래 네 말이 맞아
이 건 그냥 하나의 모습에 불과해
Just like your little stint on yearbook.
네 졸업 앨범에 있는 정액처럼 말야
You stuck with that for, what,
two weeks before you got bored with it?
네가 지루해 지기 2주 전에는
좋아했었잖아, 안 그래?
Why is it so hard for you to believe
that I wanna
넌 도대체 왜
그렇게 못 믿어?
(ON PA) wait until marriage?
난 결혼 전까지
기다리고 싶어
NATHAN ON PA.
Because you slept with Doug Wheeler
왜냐면 넌 더그 휠러
and Scott Thompson on the same night.
그리고 스캇 톰슨이랑
같은 날 잤잖아
DANA: That doesn't count: I was drunk.
그 건 계산에 포함 안 되잖아
내가 취했었으니깐
(WHISPERING) Is that Dana?
저 거 다나야?
As soon as you get bored
with this whole pledge thing,
네가 이 서약인가
뭔가에 지루해 지면
you're just gonna jump right back
in the saddle again.
넌 또 다시
남자들이랑 잘 거잖아
And when you get to college,
don't even tell me
그리고 나서 대학에 가겠지
that you won't be experimenting
with the standard lesbian hookups,
나한테 네가 레즈비언이랑
애널 섹스했다고
having three-ways, trying anal.
말도 안 하고 말이지
(ALL GASPING)
- Yeah.
좋아
That's what I'm talking...
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY) Fine: Just relax.
그만 하게
- Do something!
- PRIEST: Faith is: : .
- She's your daughter.
- Go!
믿음은 돌처럼 단단한
PRIEST: Faith is the rock-solid: : .
내가 그 걸 말할 거 같아?
우리 부모님은 결혼할 때까지 기다렸어
DANA: You don't think I'm committed to this?
My parents waited until marriage.
우리 아빠가
너희 엄마와 동창이야
NATHAN: (LAUGHS) My dad
went to high school with your mom.
너희 엄마가 풋볼팀 애들
모두 다 하고
He said she blew the whole football team
섹스했다고 하던데
and had to have her stomach pumped.
(ALL GASPING)
저속하게 굴지 말래?
DANA: Don't be gross, okay?
게다가 너희 아버지는
베타였다던데
Plus, your dad was a Beta.
베타가 좀 유명하잖아
Those guys are notorious poon slayers.
엿 먹어!
모두 다 헛소리야!
Fuck it! This is bullshit!
(PEOPLE MUTTERING)
너도 원하잖아
You know you want this.
저희 성찬식 놓쳤어요?
Did we miss communion?
(STUDENTS CHEERING)
이스트 그레이트 폴스에게
COMMENTATOR 1 ON PA.
Been a rough go for the
어려운 경기가 되고
East Great Falls Blazers in this game.
화이팅, 블레이저스!
CHEERLEADERS:
Go, Blazers!
놀랍게도 이 게 이번 시즌
마지막 홈 경기죠
: : : Which is surprising, since this is
the last home game of the season.
최선을 다할 거라는
생각이 드는데
You'd think they'd really
pump up the power there.
쟤를 봐!
쟤를 보라고!
Look at him! Watch that guy!
Watch that guy!
점점 동점이 되고 있는데요
좀 더 수비를
Even though it's close to a tie,
we were hoping for better defence from the: : .
오 세상에
근데 아버지가 뭐라고 하셨어?
Oh, my gosh, wait.
So, what did your dad say?
아버지가 네이슨보고
100피트 이내로
He said if he ever sees Nathan
within 100 feet of me,
나한테 접근하면
거세한다고 했어
he's gonna castrate him
with a rusty Garden Weasel.
오, 그래서?
너네 둘 끝난거야 뭐야?
Oh, no. So what?
Is it over between you guys or what?
나도 몰라
I don't know.
네가 만약 하고 싶다면
리차드와 난 환영이야
Well, if you ever want to try a m?age,
you're welcome to join Richard and me.
됐어
- No.
코치 데일리 주변에서
젊은이라고 하지 마세요
COMMENTATOR 1: Please don't say
"young boy" around Coach Daly.
COMMENTATOR 2 ON PA.
Yeah, out here he's: : .
넌 어때, 아가씨?
뭐가?
- What about you, missy?
- What?
네 성생활은 어때?
How's your sex life?
곧 끝낼거야
정말이야
You guys, I'm gonna go through with it.
I am. I am.
너 정말 지루하다
난 네가 도서관에서
스트립쇼한 후에
You're so boring.
I would've thought you'd be fielding offers
방어적인 자세로
나올 줄 알았어
after your striptease in the library.
난 그냥 아직 적당한 때를
기다리고 있어
Yeah, I'm...
I'm still just waiting for the right time.
블루 앤 화이트
싸워서 이기자
CHEERLEADERS: Blue and white,
let's go, fight, win. Let's go, fight, win.
블루 앤 화이트
싸워서 이기자 블레이저스!
Blue and white, let's go, fight, win. Blazers!
싸워서 이기자
블루 앤 화이트 싸워서 이기자
Fight, win.
Blue and white, let's go, fight, win.
(CAMERA CLICKING)
치어리더는 그 정도면
많이 찍은 거 같은데요
I think that is quite enough pictures
of the cheerleaders.
이제 경기 사진이나 찍는 게 어때요?
How about we get some of the game?
(CAMERA CLICKING)
(GRUNTS)
계속 하시죠
As you were.
병신
Douche bag.
블루 앤 화이트
CHEERLEADERS: Blue and white...
시어슨이 코트로
공을 가져옵니다
COMMENTATOR 1.
Shearson's bringing the ball up court.
스캇 스티플러에게
패스합니다
He passes it off to Scott Stifler.
(STUDENTS EXCLAIM)
센트럴이 시어슨에게
책임을 묻네요
Central takes a charge from Shearson.
경기를 잠시 중단합니다
자 이제 어떻게 되는거죠, 빌?
Time out, Blazers.
What are we gonna do now, Bill?
COMMENTATOR 2.
Ten seconds in the game.
I think these guys
really need to get their act: : .
집중 좀 해, 강아지 스타일*
(강아지 동영상 때문)
야한 생각은 나중에 해
Get your head in the game, doggy style.
You can finish your wet dream later.
미안해
- I'm sorry.
- This is it for this game.
스캇 우리 얘기 좀 할래?
Hey, Scott? Can I talk
to you for a sec?
너 미쳤어?
지금 경기 중이잖아
- Are you nuts? I'm in the middle of a game.
- Last home game of the season.
(GIGGLES)
협동심이 중요한
순간입니다
Really gotta get their act together.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
3.9초가 남은 지금 89점으로
동점입니다 어떻게 되나 지켜보죠
Tie game, 89 all, 3:9 seconds left.
Let's see what's gonna happen here.
센트럴이 공을 잡았습니다
블레이저스 화이팅!
- Central's got the ball.
- CHEERLEADERS: Go, Blazers!
센트럴이 유리한
입장인데요
They have the advantage.
더블 스크린을
시도합니다
Looks like: : : Double screen!
시어슨이 공을 잡아
스티플러에게 패스합니다
공이 들어갔습니다!
Shearson gets the ball.
He passes it to Scott Stifler:
It's good! It's in!
(BUZZER BUZZING)
91대89로 이스트 그레이트 폴스가
우승합니다
The game's over.
91-89 for East Great Falls Blazers.
여러분 정말 대단하지 않습니까
우리가 플레이오프에
진출한다는 말이지
This is incredible, folks!
This means we're going on to the playoffs!
믿기지 않네요
Unbelievable!
It's exciting.
오늘 정말 많은 일이
일어나네요
What a chain of events
that has occurred here today!
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
아가 우리 얘기 좀 할래
Honey, I need to talk to you.
네 그럼요
Yeah, sure.
저거 성경이니?
Is...Is that a Bible?
네?
아뇨 저건
What? No. No, it's...
성경 가지고 뭘 그러니
꼭 무슨
Well, honey, it's okay to read the Bible.
I mean, gosh, you act like
포르노라도 되는 것처럼
그러는 구나
I caught you reading pornography.
(FORCED LAUGH)
무슨 얘기 하러
오신 거예요?
What did you wanna talk about?
신용카드 명세서를 받았는데
Well, I just got
my credit card statement and...
속옷가게에서
썼다고 나왔길래
And here on your card
there's a charge here for a lingerie store.
제가 갚을게요
Yeah, I'm...
I'm gonna pay you back for that, Mom.
너 만나는 애 있니?
Is there a girl you're seeing?
아뇨 좀 복잡한 문제예요
No. Mom, it's complicated.
-그럼 네 거 산 거니?
-아뇨
- Did you buy something for yourself?
- No!
왜냐면 그런 게 흔해서
Because it's a very normal area
of exploration.
책에 보니까 페티쉬 성향의
사람은 게이가 아니라더구나
My book says that most fetishes are not
homosexual in nature,
보통 남자애들이
and, well, you know, boys, they tend to...
사실 그 거예요
제가 여자 속옷 입는 걸
좋아해서요
Yes, Mom, that's it. You figured it out.
I love wearing women's underwear.
가죽끈, G-스트링 이런 거요
Thongs, G-strings,
a little teddy now and then.
촉감이 좋더라구요
프릴이 많으면 더 좋구요
It's so soft and silky smooth.
The frillier the better.
섹시한데
Sexy.
야
이리 와
Oh, God! Come on.
찍었지롱
Gotcha.
(HUMMING)
(HISSING)
그래서 여자 주려고
샀다고?
So it was for a girl.
네, 엄마
Yeah, Mom.
알았다
Great.
그럼 너 댄스파티 전부터
알고 있었던 거야?
So, you know that thing
you told me before the dance?
응
Yeah.
내가 우리가 했던
얘기를 생각해 봤는데
Right, well,
I was thinking about that conversation.
그래서?
So, what about it?
난 네가 기다려야
한다고 생각해
I was just thinking, you know,
maybe you should wait.
알아
나도 생각해 봤어
I know. You know,
I've thought about it, too,
하지만 난 이 걸 매우
중요하게 생각해
but I still feel like
I'm making this whole thing
계속 이 생각만 나
into, like, this huge deal. I mean,
it's consuming my every thought.
(SIGHS)
롭 나도 모르겠어
I don't know, Rob.
내 생각엔 그냥
끝내버리는 게 최선인 거 같아
I still feel like it's best
if I just get it over with.
그래 이해해
Yeah. I can see that.
사실 그 거예요
제가 여자 속옷 입는 걸
좋아해서요
ROB ON PHONE: You figured it out.
I love wearing women's underwear.
가죽끈, G-스트링 이런 거요
Thongs, G-strings,
a little teddy now and then.
촉감이 좋더라구요
프릴이 많으면 더 좋구요
It's so soft and silky smooth.
The frillier the better.
이 쓰레기는 뭐야
엉덩아?
What is up with this crap, butt nugget?
앞뒤 상황이 안 찍혀서 그래
그냥 농담한 거야
That was taken completely out of context.
All right? I was being facetious.
농담은 사실이
아니란 뜻이야
That means he wasn't being serious.
나도 농담이 뭔지 알아
멍청아
I know what facetious means, dick face.
학교 여자애들을
다 쫓아버리려고 작정했냐?
Are you trying to repel
all the pussy in school?
아니
똑딱똑딱, 강아지야
- No...
- Tick tock, doggy boy.
네 똘똘이가 급하시단다
You cock is on the clock.
실례할게
잘 보고 배워
Excuse me. Take notes.
안녕 이모진
스티플러
- Hey, lmogen.
- Stifler.
오늘의 단어는 "다리"야
The word for the day is "legs:"
그래서?
So?
우리 집에 가서 단어를
퍼트려 보는 게 어때?
So, why don't we go back to my place
and spread the word?
글쎄 네 목숨부터
챙기시지?
Well, how about you save your breath?
데이트 얘기를 부풀리려면
목숨이 필요할거야
You're gonna need it
to inflate your date later.
신사분들
이제 작업을 할 시간입니다
Gentlemen, it is time we got laid.
뭐? 우리가 지금까지
한 건 뭔데?
Really? And what is it
we've been trying to do all this time?
아니 우린 실전 연습을
해야 한다고 여길 봐
1995년 9월 9일
No, no. We need to get laid.
Right here. September 9th, 1995.
요약 해서 말해 줄래?
Can you give us the executive summary?
아니 그 거 말고
이 거
No, not that. This.
우린 여행을 갈 거야
LUBE: We are going on a road trip.
캐나다에서 얼마나 있을 거니?
How long do you intend
on staying in Canada?
한 두 시간 정도요
Just a couple of hours.
뭐 하러 온 거니?
What's the nature of your visit?
여성의 은밀한 부위를 맛보기
위해 수 십 마일을 왔어요
We've driven many miles
in search of vertical smiles.
(BOYS LAUGHING)
여기선 킬로미터를 쓴단다
We use kilometres here.
그럼 똘똘이에게 물을 주려고
수 십 킬로를 왔어요
Then we've driven many clicks
to wet our dicks?
그래!
그 거야!
LUBE: Yes!
ROB: Yeah!
그럼 됐죠?
수고하세요
- That works, right?
- Bye-bye.
(LAUGHS)
멍청한 미국인들
Fucking Americans.
(BOYS CHEERING)
환율때문에 이득을
볼 거 같아
You know, the exchange rate on the dollar
is really gonna help us out.
신난다
Yeah.
쭉 가다가 오른쪽으로
돌면 돼
Okay, up ahead, turn right.
-확실해?
-그래 오른쪽이야
- You sure?
- Yes. Turn right.
좋아
그럼 해 볼까
Okay, boys. Let's do this.
정말 잘 하고 있는 걸까?
Are you sure this is a good idea?
겁쟁아 왜 그래
어서 작업해야지
Come on, you pussy.
Let's get laid.
성경에 보면
모니크를 찾으래
The bible says to ask for Monique.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
안녕하세요
모니크인가요?
Hi. Are you Monique?
아냐 아냐
모니크는 안에 있어
(IN FRENCH ACCENT) No, moi, no, no, no.
Mais, Monique, she is inside.
어서 들어오렴
Come. Come, boys.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
(POP SONG PLAYING)
얘들아
Boys, entrez chez nous.
모니크를 불러 올 게
C'est magnifique, no?
I will get Monique.
너희를 보면 좋아할거야
She will be so happy to see you.
그 동안 편안히
있으렴
In the meantime, make yourselves at home.
(EXCLAIMS)
야 꼭지들 좀 봐
제대로 온 거 같은데
Jesus, tits. We came to the right place.
저 거 무스(moose)야?
Is that a moose?
콘돔 드려요?
Condom?
고마워요
Why, thank you.
Gentlemen.
신사분
Thank you.
매우
고마워요
Very much.
Thank you.
모니크가 누굴지 궁금하다
LUBE: Can't wait to see Monique.
(DOOR OPENING)
(ALL GASP)
저흰 모니크를
만나러 왔어요
(STAMMERING) We're here to see Monique.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
내가 모니크란다
(IN FRENCH ACCENT) I am Monique.
Oh! ... Well, that's...That's okay.
아니에요.. 괜찮아요
이리 오렴
좋은 술을 줄게
Come, come. I make you a nice drink.
(BONE CRACKS)
(GRUNTING)
Yeah, could you just
give us just one minute?
잠깐 저희끼리 얘기
좀 해도 될까요?
This could be very
educational for all of us.
Really?
- He's up.
- No, no. Why am I first?
-얘가 먼저예요
-싫어 왜 하필 나야?
NATHAN: It was your idea.
네 생각이었잖아
모니크를 모욕하지마
책에서 한 챕터나 나오잖아
Don't...Don't insult Monique.
She has an entire chapter in the bible.
이리 오렴
재밌을 거야
LUBE: (LAUGHS)
You two crazy kids have fun.
둘이서 재밌게 놀아
(WOMAN SPEAKING FRENCH)
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
환영한다
And welcome.
So...So, how does this work?
Am I supposed to pay you?
어떻게 하면 되죠?
제가 돈을 드려야 하나요?
아니
아직 아냐
No, no, no. Not yet.
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
(LAUGHS)
Oh, I see.
알았어요
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
(UNZIPPING PANTS)
(MOANING)
상상력이 참 풍부하구나
꼬마야
You've got one active imagination, boy.
(GASPS)
How long was I out for?
나 얼마 동안
이러고 있었어?
Only about eight seconds that time.
한 8초 정도
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
(BONE CRACKING)
(GROANS)
안 돼
하지 마요
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No. No. No, no, no.
Yes. Yes.
오 좋아
(MOANING)
(ROB MOANING LOUDLY)
모니크
정말 죽여줘요
ROB: Monique! Oh!
That's really nice.
(CLACKING)
ROB: That's it.
그래 이 거야
I'm so sorry. I
usually last a lot longer.
죄송해요
평소엔 오래 가는데
Hey.
저기요
Hey, was I supposed to
tap you on the shoulder or something?
제가 어깨를 잡거나
뭐 그래야 하나요?
Oh, no. No.
오 안 돼
Help! Help! Help, help, help!
도와줘요! 도와줘요!
NATHAN: Go, go, go! Go!
LUBE: I'm coming!
가자!
내가 갈 게!
- Jesus. Dude.
- Oh, God!
-야 인마
-이 게 뭐야!
What, do you need an audience?
너 하는 거
구경하라고 불렀냐?
No, no. Wait, guys.
I think she's dead!
아니 그 게 아니라
모니크가 죽은 거 같아
Excuse me?
뭐라고?
Oh, my God. This is not good.
어떡해
어쩌면 좋아
I can't get her off.
I think she had a heart attack.
모니크를 떼어 낼 수가 없어
심장마비인가 봐
Help! She's got lockjaw.
Get her off of me!
도와줘! 파상풍인가 봐
어서 떼어 내
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
- It's lockjaw.
-어떡하지
-파상풍이라고!
Lockjaw! Lockjaw, lockjaw, lockjaw,
lockjaw, lockjaw!
파상풍 파상풍!
- Okay.
- Get her off!
-알았어
-어서 떼어 내
(ALL CLAMOURING)
I'm sorry!
미안!
(SCREAMING)
Phone. Phone. Wait. Clear!
전화기 전화기
기다려 됐다!
Shit. What am I doing?
젠장
내가 뭐하는 거지?
Clear, clear!
자 됐어!
(SCREAMING)
Okay. Come down here.
Grab her legs. One, two, three.
이리 와서 다리를 잡아
하나 둘 셋
Forget it. It's totally screwed up. Oh, God.
이제 완전 망했어
(DOOR OPENING)
(MAN SPEAKING FRENCH)
What you do to maman?
우리 엄마한테
무슨 짓이야?
(SHRIEKS)
(BOYS SCREAMING)
(CRYING) Maman! You killed maman!
You killed maman!
엄마! 네가 엄마를 죽였어
엄마를 죽였다고!
(ROARING)
Fucking Americans! Come back here.
I'll kill you! I'll kill you, you cowards!
엿 같은 미국인들! 이리 와
죽여버릴거야! 이 겁쟁이들아
ROB: I killed her.
내가 죽였어
I killed her with my sperm!
내 정액 때문에 죽었어
Hey, man, when it's your time to go,
it's your time to go. She led a full life.
원래 때가 되면 죽는 거야
모니크는 살만큼 살았잖아
How do you know that?
네가 그 걸 어떻게 알아?
Man, what do you want me to say?
You're the one that murdered her!
야 그럼 나보고 어떡하라고
네가 죽였잖아!
I can't believe that was the woman
the bible said we should have sex with.
우리가 섹스해야 될 여자가
모니크라는 게 안 믿겨
Right here: "September 9th, 1995:"
여길 봐 1995년 9월 9일
Let me see that.
내가 볼 게
No. No, that's a seven!
That's 1975. It's from the '70s.
이 건 7이잖아
1975년이야
- I thought it was a nine.
- NATHAN: Shut up! Shut up!
-난 9인 줄 알았어
-닥쳐 닥쳐!
- I didn't do anything!
- Shut up! Just shut up! I wanna go home.
-난 아무 짓도 안 했어
-그냥 좀 닥쳐! 집에 가고 싶어
I don't wanna be here.
나도 여기 있기 싫어
(THUDS)
Oh, my God! I just hit a squirrel.
내가 다람쥐를 쳤어
LUBE: Well, that went well.
잘 하네
ROB: Guys, I think it's time
we try my interpretation.
이제 내 방법을
쓸 때가 왔어
Look, Nathan, you've been trying to
convince Dana to sleep with you,
네이슨 넌 항상 다나의
말은 듣지 않고
instead of just listening to her.
Right, you know?
너랑 자야 한다고
설득하려고 했어
Trying to see things from her point of view?
Showing just...
다나의 관점으로
보려고 해 봐
Just a little respect.
조금이라도
존중한다는 걸 보여 줘
And you, you're still trying
to trick women into sleeping with you,
그리고 넌 여자애들이
너랑 자게 하려고
instead of just being honest.
속이고 다녔잖아
And you're still too much of a pussy
to tell Heidi you're into her.
그러는 넌 겁쟁이라
하이디한테 좋다고 말도 못 하지
You going to Stifler's house tonight?
오늘 스티플러 집에 가?
Yeah. I'll probably go with Dana.
응
아마 다나랑 갈 거야
So any luck losing that thing you were
trying to get rid of?
네가 없애려고
하는 건 없앴어?
- Rob.
- I'm just asking.
-롭
-그냥 궁금해서
Maybe you should mind your own business.
네 일이나
신경쓰지 그래
What's with you today?
오늘 무슨 일 있어?
I wanna tell you something that
I've been wanting to say for a long time.
너에게 오래 전부터
말해주고 싶은 게 있어
Okay.
말해 봐
I really like you.
난 네가 좋아
I really like you, too.
나도 네가 좋아
No, not like that.
I really like you.
아니 그런 식으로
좋다는 게 아니라
Oh.
오
- Rob...
- I think you're great.
-롭
-넌 정말 멋져
You have a great personality.
I laugh at all your jokes. You're pretty.
넌 성격도 좋고 재밌어
그리고 예뻐
Oh, God, you're pretty.
You even smell great.
넌 정말로 예뻐
심지어 좋은 냄새도 나
I don't know. I'm just...
I'm happy when I'm around you.
이상하게 네 곁에만
있으면 행복해져
Now, I don't know if you feel the same way,
but if you do...
너도 나처럼 느끼는지
모르겠지만
Let's not waste any more time. Right?
Let's just
이제 더 이상 시간 낭비하지 말자
서로의 감정이
see where our feelings take us.
어디로 이끄는지
지켜보는 거야
I feel the same way.
나도 너와
같은 생각이야
- You do?
- Yes.
-정말?
-그래
This is great.
Why didn't you say something?
좋은데
왜 아무 말도 안했어?
Why didn't you?
그러는 넌?
(LAUGHING)
(CELL PHONE BUZZING)
It's about that time, so I gotta go.
But I'll see you tonight?
이제 가야 겠어
오늘 밤에 보는 거지?
Yes.
응
- DANA: Dad?
- Mmm-hmm?
-아빠?
-응?
There she is.
저다
(GASPING) They saw me!
Get down! Get down!
-날 봤어!
-엎드려 엎드려
- Oh, my God. Oh, my gosh.
- Drive. Drive.
-어떡해
-운전해 운전해
It's cool. It's cool.
침착해지자
Nathan, look, I've been thinking.
네이슨 내가 생각을
해봤는데
Maybe I've been too hard on you.
내가 너무 한 거 같구나
You have?
정말요?
You obviously love my daughter,
and you two should be together.
-진짜요?
-물론
- We should?
- Absolutely.
아가 남자보고
참으라고 하면 못 쓴다
Honey, it is not right
to give a man blue balls.
남자애들이 좋아해 주길
바라면 먼저 다가가야 해
우선 네이슨 친구부터 하자
If you want boys to like you, you gotta
put out. Here, start with Nathan's friend.
이건 좀 아니잖아
This is so not cool.
네 친구의 여친을 상상해?
I mean, fantasising about
your best friend's girlfriend?
오 맙소사
(SCREAMING) Oh, my God!
-아빠 그만해요
-꺼져 버려!
- Dad! Stop! Stop.
- Fucknut!
(ALL CHEERING)
All right, girls.
- Party looks good.
- Yeah.
-파티 괜찮은데
-그러게
Uh-huh.
맞아
All right, listen to me. Stay focused.
좋아 잘 들어
집중해
Be honest, show respect
and just say whatever's on your mind.
솔직하게 존경심을
보이고 네 마음을 말해
Stop, jerk.
그만해 멍청아
난 다나 근처에도 못 가
I can't even get near Dana.
She'll be here.
She's coming with Heidi.
하이디랑 같이
온다고 했어
Just try and think of things
from her point of view.
그냥 다나의 관점으로
보려고 해 봐
Yeah, and I might as well just crack
the Da Vinci Code while I'm at it.
그래 그러다보면
독심술이라도 하겠네
솔직하게 굴고
뇌물이라도 주지 그래
Just get her some frankincense and myrrh.
That's a great idea.
좋은 생각인데
내가 루피라도 좀
가져다 줄 게
(루피: 데이트 강간약)
I'll just pick up some roofies for you
while I'm out.
그 거 처방전 필요할 걸
You need a prescription for that,
from what I hear.
Lube, pay attention.
This applies to you, too.
루브 집중해
너한테도 해당하는 말이야
All right.
Let's try to go in there and just be real.
좋아 들어가서
솔직하게 하면 돼
All right, Oprah.
알았어 오프라
(오프라 윈프리를 빗대어 비꼼)
(POP MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey. Isn't that that chick from Central?
맞아
Yeah.
안녕 스티플러
Hey, Stifler.
오 안녕..
Oh, hey, there...
케이티야
Katie.
맞아 케이티
저번에 재밌었지
Katie, right. I knew that.
Just having some fun with you.
우리 둘이 잠깐
얘기 좀 해
Can I talk to you for a second,
like, in private?
그럼 물론이지
Yeah, sure, you know what?
맥주 가지러
갔다가 올 게
Let me just grab another beer
and I'll be right back with you.
도망 가지마
Don't you flake on me.
야 잘 되고 있어?
별로
Dude, you been working out?
Didn't think so.
둘 다 끝내주는데
You two, stay amazing. My God.
(GIGGLES)
여긴 무슨 일이야
이쁜이?
Hey, what's up, beautiful?
저번주에 너무 취해서
You know, I got so drunk last weekend
똘똘이랑 탁자와 놀았더니만
불이 나지 뭐야
that I nailed my cock to a table,
then set it on fire.
보고 싶어?
Wanna check it out?
탁자 아님 똘똘이?
The table or your cock?
네 억양 죽인다
God, I love that accent.
"때려줘요 스티플러
엉덩이를 때려줘요"라고
Could you do me
a favour and just say,
말해 줄래?
"Spank me, Stifler.
Spank me wee little bum:"
내가 맞는 거 좋아하는 거
어떻게 알았어?
How did you know
I like to be spanked?
죽~인다
(IN HIGH
-PITCHED VOICE) Awesome!
네가 맨날 말하는
리차드는 어딨냐?
So where's this boyfriend Richard you keep
talking about non-stop all the time?
리차드는 고등학교
파티는 안 와
He doesn't attend high-school parties.
꼭 네가 어른들이랑(American beef)
사귄다는 것처럼 들리는데
American beef: 쇠고기, 근육질 남자
Sounds like you might be in the market
for some home-grown American beef.
미안 채식주의자야
Sorry, I'm vegan.
건배
Cheers.
내가 오이를 쓴다면 어때?
What if I use a cucumber?
All right, boys. Tonight's the night.
Wish me luck.
잘 해
Good luck, buddy.
오늘 밤 넌 남자가 되는 거야
Good luck, dude.
Tonight, you become a man.
그래 그 거야
오늘 밤 드디어 잔다!
That's it. Tonight,
I'm getting laid!
- Yeah, buddy! Yes!
- Yeah, buddy.
그래
좋아
- Yes!
- Right here.
좋아
처음엔 천천히
부드럽게 하다가
Just give it to her
nice and slow at first.
점점 속력을 내는 거야
Then speed her up.
다나
D.. Dana!
Dana!
Yeah!
(WHOOPS)
Yeah! Woooh!
- What?
- Sorry.
- I can't find Heidi anywhere.
- Maybe she didn't come.
아냐 밖에
차가 있단 말야
No, no. Her car is outside.
넌 어떻게 돼 가?
How you making out?
저기 봐
Check it out.
너 애슐리는 좀 무리라고
생각 안 해?
Don't you think maybe Ashley's
just a little bit out of your league?
네가 몇 년 동안
공들였지만
I don't know. I'm just saying, you know,
you've been at it for years.
애슐리는 네 짝이
아닌 거 같아
Maybe it's just not
in the cards for you.
난 치밀한 남자야
I'm a man of refinement.
10점짜리가 있는데
왜 6점짜리를 갖겠어?
Why settle for a six
when you can get a perfect 10?
네가 좋다면야
잘 해 봐
Okay, whatever you say, man. Good luck.
좋아
난 할 수 있다
I'm gonna do it.
애슐리 안녕?
Hey, what's up, Ashley?
Hey, Lube.
안녕 루브
You want a beer?
맥주 줄까?
마시고 있어
Got a beer.
그렇구나
Right.
저기
So...
너도 내가 너 좋아하는 거
알지?
You obviously know that I'm,
like, totally into you. Right?
그럼
네가 날 숭배하는 걸 알지
Yeah. I've seen the shrine.
(LAUGHS)
좋아
All right.
솔직하게 말 할게
Okay, so I'm just gonna be honest with you.
I'm just gonna lay it out on the line.
속임수도 없고
정말 솔직하게
No tricks, no hidden agenda at all.
내가 어쩌다가 감각적인
사랑의 전문가가 되었어
I happen to be
a sensitive and expert lover.
(GIRLS LAUGHING)
네가 만족할 거라고
보증할 수 있어
I can guarantee that I will satisfy you
in every way possible,
그리고 네가 만족할 때까지
and I shall not stop until I'm certain
절대 멈추지 않을 거야
that you are completely happy
with my endeavours.
알았어
Okay.
(SIGHS)
네 얘기가 재밌긴 해
Look, that was a really interesting speech,
널 망신시키고 싶진 않지만
and I don't really wanna embarrass you
in front of everyone, but...
그럴 일은 없을 거야
But it's not gonna happen.
넌 멋지고
I mean, I think that you're,
like, really super cool,
정말 재밌어
and you're really funny in class
and everything,
하지만 섹스는
하고 싶지 않아
but I don't wanna have sex with you.
알았지?
Okay?
응 그래
Yeah, yeah. Sure. Okay.
-그럼 우리 괜찮은 거지?
-물론
- So are we cool?
- Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
알았어
All right.
맥주 가지러 갈 건데
너도 줄까?
Well, I'm gonna go get another beer.
Do you want one?
아냐 됐어
No, no. I'm...I'm good. I'm good.
-안녕
- Hey.
네가 아까 한 말
(CLEARS THROAT) What you said just now?
응?
Yeah?
진짜야?
Was that true?
만족을 보증하고 여자가
만족할 때까지 안 멈춘다며
Guaranteed satisfaction and you won't stop
until a girl is completely satisfied?
응
Yeah.
좋아
에라 모르겠다
All right. Well, what the hell.
윗 층 왼쪽에서
첫번째 방으로 와
Meet me upstairs
in the first bedroom to the left.
(LAUGHS)
사실 내가 널
부담스럽게 하긴 했어
NATHAN: The truth is, yes,
I was trying to pressure you,
왜냐면 너무 섹스가
하고 싶었거든
because I really, really wanna have sex.
근데 진짜 너랑
섹스하고 싶어
But I really wanna have sex with you.
물론 우리가 함께하는 한
섹스는 나의 관심분야일 거야
And, also, I mean, with us,
hooking up has always been about me.
단 한 번이라도
널 기쁘게 해 주고 싶었어
I wanna forget myself for once
and try to make you feel good for a change.
네가 좋다면야
나도 행복해
Like, maybe try and make you feel
the way that you make me feel.
Oh!
(PHONE BEEPS)
오
Oh.
하지마
그 건 내 핸드폰이야
You shouldn't...You shouldn't...
It's my phone.
제발 보지마
Don't read my phone.
이 게 무슨 말이야?
"여자애한테 약을 잔뜩 주라고"?
What's this supposed to mean?
"Give her a dose of manthrax"?
나도 그 게
뭔지 모르겠어
Well, I don't...
What does that...
정말 모르겠는데
넌 뭔지 알겠어?
I don't know what that...
Do you know what that means?
"나 섹스 한다"?
"I'm getting laid"?
하기도 전에 이미
광고를 해?
You're advertising this
before it even happens?
-아냐
-와
- No.
- Wow.
너 정말 재수없는
새끼구나
You must be some special kind of asshole.
아냐 그 게 아니라
난..
No. No, no, no! No. I didn't...It was...
(GRUNTS ANGRILY)
다음에 보자
찌질아
Later, loser.
빨리 오 좋아
천천히 좋아
Faster. Okay. Now, slower. Yes, yes.
천천히 핥아
좋아
Slower. Tickle the bunny. Yes, yes.
맙소사
정말 프로같아
Oh, God, the man
in the boat is out.
어서 빨리
Paddle, paddle, do the alphabet. Swirl.
다시 핥아
그래 그 거야 더 왼쪽으로
Back to the bunny. That's it.
Okay. Now, more to the left.
더 왼쪽
More to the left!
-내 왼쪽 네 왼쪽?
-내 왼쪽!
- My left or your left?
- My left, my left, my left!
좋아
All right.
하이디 봤어?
Hey, have you seen Heidi?
고마워
Thanks.
안녕 롭
Hey, Rob.
하이디?
Heidi?
안녕 강아지 스타일
내가 그랬지 넌 졌어
Hey, doggy style.
I told you, you snooze, you lose.
청소하러 온 거 아니면
문 닫아 변태야
So unless you want mop-up duty,
close the door, pervert.
(STIFLER GIGGLES)
하이디 어디가?
STIFLER: Hey, where are you going?
이 건 정말
나쁜 생각이었어
This was a horrible idea.
롭?
실례할게요
Rob? Excuse me.
롭! 롭!
Excuse me. Rob. Rob.
-저리 가
-난..
- Go away.
- I didn't. l...
지금 네 얼굴 보고
싶지 않아
I don't wanna see your face right now.
롭
Rob.
(GASPING)
(LAUGHS)
Whoa, whoa.
지금 뭐하는 거야?
What are you doing?
날 위해 널 희생한다며?
What happened to forgetting about yourself
and making me feel good?
아니 난 그냥
But I thought I just...
무슨 생각인데
네이슨?
What? You thought that what, Nathan?
날 위해 주는 척
하려고 한 거였어?
That you could just pretend that you cared
about my feelings and my pledge
그리고 나서 나랑
자려고 그런 거지?
and then just go
and try again when my guard was down?
아냐 그 게 아냐
No. You don't get it. l...
아니
못 알아 듣는 건 너야
No. No, you're the one
that's not gonna get it.
천천히 마셔
Dude, you need to slow down.
그래 정말
이제 집에 가자
Yeah, seriously.
Let's just go home.
저기 네가 책에 대해
말한 게 맞았어
You, sir...
You, sir, were right about the bible.
왜냐면 나쁜 놈들이
여자를 얻거든
Because assholes get laid!
(BOYS CHEERING)
맞아!
Yes.
아냐 아냐
네가 맞아
No. No, no, dude.
You were right.
-그 게 전부가 아냐
-무슨 말하는 거야?
- There's something to it.
- What are you talking about?
우린 착하게 굴려고 했는데
여전히 총각이잖아
We tried the nice guy thing
and I believe we're all still virgins.
근데 그 착한 남자 방법이
나한테는 먹히던데
Well, the nice guy vibe got me
past the bouncer, man.
안녕
Hey.
근데 있잖아, 넌 실패했어
그리고 정답은 바로 젤리야
Well, gentlemen, you failed,
and the proof, as they say, is in the Jell-o.
그럼 나중에 보자
착한 남자들
So I will see you later, nice guys.
-안녕
- Hey.
네가 날
원하는 걸 알아
I know you want me.
그러니까 어서 윗층으로
가서 하자
I'm gonna let you take me upstairs
and do me right now.
-정말?
-응
- Really?
- Yeah.
키스해
Kiss me.
고통을 맛 볼
준비 됐어?
STIFLER: Y'all ready for some pain?
이 봐
아가씨들
Hey, ladies.
(GIRLS SCREAMING)
GIRL: Oh, my God.
이 것 보게
STIFLER: Oh, my God!
가슴 좀 봐!
Look at those taters!
뒤로 하자
Do me from behind.
뭐?
What?
네가 개처럼 하는 걸
좋아하는 줄 알았는데
I thought you liked it doggy style.
뭐?
ROB: Huh?
뒤에서 뭐 해?
어서 해
What are you doing back there? Let's go.
네 똘똘이 안 넣을 거지
그렇지?
You're not putting your dick in that,
are you?
(SCREAMS)
장난해?
역겨워
Are you kidding me? Gross.
(THUDS)
(GROANS)
이 거 마시렴
Here. This'll help.
고마워요
Thanks.
내가 너보고 하지 말라고
할 순 없다는 걸 알지만
Honey, I know that I can't stop you
from doing certain things,
그래도 네 안전을
생각해야지
but I can insist that you are safe.
음주 운전 했니?
Did you drink and drive?
아뇨 존 코스텔로가
태워 줬어요
No. John Costello drove me home.
네가 쾌락적인 상황에
있을 때 자신을
Well, I want you to know that if
you find yourself in any carnal situation,
보호할 줄 알았으면
좋겠구나
that you...You will use protection.
쾌락이라뇨?
What do you mean by carnal?
이 거 말야
This.
(GROANS)
장난해?
역겨워
GIRL: Are you kidding me? Gross.
전 이제 더이상
사생활도 없는 거예요?
Is there no such
thing as privacy any more?
아버지한테는 네가 오늘
몸 상태가 안 좋다고 말해두마
I will tell your father that
you're just not up to seeing him today.
상태가 안 좋아
보이는구나
You're not feeling well.
고마워요
Thanks.
숙녀분은 어떻대?
How was she?
-누구 말야?
-어제 토한 여자
- How was who?
- Vomit girl.
그건 어떻게 알았어?
How do you know about that?
누가 이런 걸 엄마한테
보냈겠어?
Who do you think is forwarding
all those videos to Mom?
이젠 포기다
정말
ROB: I'm ready to give up.
내가 정답을 알고
있다고 생각했어
I thought I had the answers.
책 내용 중 99%는
읽을 수 없다는 게 안타까워
It's too bad that 99% of the bible's
completely unreadable.
그 거야
That's it.
우리가 성경을
복원하는 거야
We need to reconstruct the bible.
왜?
Why?
비밀이 이 안에 있어
The secrets are in there.
그러니까 여자와 자기 위한
비법이 어딘 가에 있을 거야
I mean, there's no one single answer
to getting laid.
우린 책의 일부가 아닌
전체가 필요한 거였어
Right? We need the whole book
to understand.
분명히 우리가 꼭 알아야
할 여러 비법이 있을 거야
Probably has a lot of crap in there
that we need to know, too,
자세, 기술, 삽입의 각도
같은 것들 말야
like positions, techniques,
angle of insertion.
이 책은 바로 우리 같은
초보를 위해 만들어진 거니까
Exactly. That's what the bible was
created for, to help guys like us.
내가 성경을 망쳤으니
지식을 이어 받을 후배들에게
And we owe it to the others.
I ruined the bible.
빚을 지고 있는 셈이지
I owe it to future generations
to restore its wisdom.
나도 복원하고 싶어
근데 어떻게 하게?
Dude, I'm all for it, but how?
어디 부터
시작하지?
Where do we start?
창조자를 찾아야지
From the beginning.
이 사람이 성경을
만든 게 분명해
LUBE: This must be the guy
who created the bible.
(RINGING)
여보세요?
Hello?
안녕하세요
노아 레빈스틴씨 계신 가요?
ROB: Hi: May I speak
to Noah Levenstein, please?
접니다
Speaking.
혹시 성경
창조자이신가요?
Are you the one who created the bible?
아뇨
아마 신이 창조했을 겁니다
No, that would be God.
저기요
잠깐만요
No, no, no: Hold on.
특별한 성경 말이에요
I'm referring to the bible.
전 이스트 그레이트 폴스
고등학교 학생이에요
I'm calling from
East Great Falls High School.
내가 3학년이던
1969년 여름이었어
NOAH: It was the summer
of my junior year, 1969,
친구들과 난 암스테르담으로
여행을 떠났는데
and my buddies and I,
we take this trip to Amsterdam,
지미 핸드릭스 LP판과
자신들을 교환하려는
where we run into a group
of semi-attractive Dutch nymphos
독일 음란녀들을 만났어
who were willing to trade their bodies
for a handful of Jimi Hendrix LPs.
말할 필요도 없이
우리는 독일녀들과
Well, needless to say, we had ourselves
one super weekend with those gals,
정말 끝내주는
한 주를 보냈지
sexually speaking, if you get my drift.
하지만 슬프게도 우리는
우리가 뭘 하는지도 몰랐어
But the sad news was,
we had no idea what we were doing.
우린 기술이 없었거든
We had no technique.
그런데 어느 날
경치를 보러 나갔는데
And then one day, we were out sight-seeing,
홍등가에서
독일 창녀들을 만났어
and we run into this Dutch hooker
in the red-light district,
그녀가 우리에게
성경에 대해 알려주더군
and she tells us about this book.
성경은 바로 19세기
성직자가 쓴 섹스 설명서였어
It was a sex manual, evidently written
in the 19th century by some priest.
우린 그 책을
샅샅이 읽고
Well, we read that thing cover to cover,
학교로 돌아왔지
and then when we got back
to East Great Falls,
근데 내가 경험을 담은
나만의 책을 만들어서
I had the bright idea
to write my own book
조언도 함께 적어놓고
and add my own observations
and experiences and advice
우리와 같은 총각이 보도록
도서관에 놔두면 어떨까 생각했지
and leave it in the library for some
other hapless virgin in the class below us.
난 그 게 40년 동안
계속 이어질 줄은 몰랐지
But I had no idea it had been
passed down for 40 years.
선배님의 성경은
정말 전설이에요
Your book is a legend,
Mr Levenstein.
혹시 가져왔니?
Do you have it here?
네
Yeah.
내가 봐도 될 까?
May I see it?
오
Oh.
오 세상에
Oh, my.
얘들아
Boys.
이 건 정말 살아있는
역사구나
This is a real piece of history here.
도대체 무슨 일이
일어난 거니?
What happened to it?
그래서 저희가 여기에
온 거예요
Well, that's why we're here.
성경이 좀 망가져서
The bible kinda got ruined,
목록에 있는 모든 사람에게
전화해서 복원해 보려구요
so we wanna call everyone on the list
and try to reconstruct it.
오
Oh.
너희들 도움이 좀
필요할 거 같구나
Well, I think you boys might need
some help.
여자애들은 이런 일에 유리하지
남자와는 달리
Well, girls have the advantage,
because girls talk to each other,
서로 얘기를 하거든
and don't kid yourself,
they talk about the penis.
페니스 모양, 사이즈,
구부러진 각도
Penis size, penis shape,
the angle of the bend.
너흰 못 알아차려도
여자들은 항상 얘길하지
Whether it winks at you. They talk.
여자와 사랑을 나누려면
진심으로 아껴줘야 해
Now, to really make love to a woman,
you gotta really care about her.
섹스는 정말 좋은 거야
네가 사랑하는
사람과 하면 더 좋지
But...Hey, sex is great, but sex with
someone you love? That's awesome.
와 정말 조예가
깊으시네요
Dude, that is so profound.
내가 말했잖아
Telling you.
그럼 지금 혼자있어
Yeah, definitely gets lonely on the road.
물론이지
난 온갖 종류의 음식을 써봤어
Sure, I made love to all kinds
of different food groups.
땅콩 버터 샌드위치
써 봤나?
Did you ever try making love
to a peanut-butter sandwich?
그만한 게 없어
Nothing comes close.
뭐라구요?
What?
뼈없는 뒷다리 햄이 좋긴
하지만 그건 준비할 게 많아
Well, maybe a deboned ham hock,
but that takes a whole lot of prep.
무릎을 꿇게
Bend your knees.
다음에 빰을 맞으면
인디언처럼 앉아 보게
Next time you spank it, sit Indian-style.
앞으로 한 몇 백년은
물어보러 안 와도 될 걸세
You won't come, not in a million years.
우리의 성기는
악기와 같아
MAN: Our sex organs
are like musical instruments.
누구든지 호른을
연주할 수는 있지
Sure, you can have any technician
blow on your horn,
하지만 진정한 달인이
연주한다면?
but to place your instrument into
the hands of a true expert?
달인은 진정한
하모니를 만들지
That, my young friend, is true harmony.
남자들은 서로 얘기를 안 해
NOAH: Guys don't talk to each other
왜냐면 서로를 경쟁자로 보거든
because they view each other
as competitors,
다들 미쳤나봐
그렇지 않니?
which I think is crazy. You know?
남자들은 합심해서 섹스할 수
있도록 서로 도와줘야 해
Because men need to help each other
and work together to get laid.
노아 레빈스틴
70년대에 다녔었죠
NO AH: Noah Levenstein, class of '70.
-피트 샘브렐리?
-맞아요 노아 레븐스틴이에요
ROB: Pete Sambrelli?
NO AH: That's right, the Noah Levenstein.
전화번호 있으세요?
ROB: Do you have a number for him?
안녕하세요
윤활제에 대한 조언을
얻으려 전화했습니다
Hi: This is regarding his advice
on the lubricants.
레자이나에서
폭풍혀를 찾았다!
We found the tongue tornado in Regina.
(BOYS CHEERING)
네가 형제들이
우선이라고 했잖아
You said bros befo' hos.
그렇게 말했잖아
그러고 나서
내 여친이랑 잤으면서!
Isn't that what you said? Bros befo' hos.
And then you screwed my girlfriend.
합창반 애들 다 그랬잖아, 칼리토
말하고 싶은 게 뭐야?
Well, so did the entire glee club, Carlito.
What's your point?
It's all about chemistry,
and confidence is the key.
존 경
그 노래 들어보셨죠?
MAN: R-E-S-P-E-C-T,
you've heard that song, right?
얘들아 새로운
증거가 들어왔단다
Boys, we got another confirmation.
숙녀분을
제대로 다뤄야 해
MAN: You gotta treat your lady right.
사랑으로 친절하고
존경심을 보여줘야 해
You've got to be gentle, kind
and respectful to the one you love.
-누구랑 통화해요?
-입 좀 닥쳐
- Who are you talking to?
- Shut the fuck up.
이렇게 하면
흥분 시킬 수 있어
This is how you get her really excited.
손가락을 항문에 넣어
내가 장담해
Stick your finger in her ass. Trust me.
한 개요 아님 두개요?
Was that two fingers or one?
죄송해요
기밀 사항이라서요
LUBE: I'm sorry.
Confidential matter.
전화받아
전화
NOAH: Phone, phone. Okay.
LUBE: Then what happened?
여보세요
네 77년 졸업이요
Hello. Yeah. Class of '77.
잠시만요
펜 좀 찾구요
Yeah, hold on.
Let me get a pen.
피트 오도넬씨죠?
Pete O'Donnell, please.
누구세요?
Who is this?
오도넬씨
마셸 루벳스키인데요
Mr O'Donnell, this is Marshall Lubetski.
성경에 쓰신 내용을
여쭤보고 싶어서요
I just wanted to talk to you about
what you wrote in the bible.
존슨 선생님과의
애널 섹스에 대해서요
You know, about having anal sex
with Miss Johnson.
(ALL CLAMOURING)
오 좋아!
마크 S에 체크해
...very much! Mark S.!
(ALL CHEERING)
이 건 섹스 설명서가 아냐
This is not a sex manual.
인생 설명서지
It is a life manual.
내가 여자를 만족시킬 줄 아는
Now, I've been married for 35 years
훈남이라 35년간 결혼을
and not just because
I'm this handsome dude
유지할 수 있었던 건 아냐
who knows how to satisfy a woman.
내가 아내를 사랑하고
I've been married 35 years
because I love my wife
존중해서 35년간 유지할 수
있었던 거야
and I respect my wife.
그리고 암스테르담이건
이스트 그레이트 고교에서든
And whether it's Amsterdam
or East Great Falls,
한 가지 결론을
내릴 수 있어
it all comes down to this.
만약 여자를 존중하고
정직하게 대한다면
If you're honest and
treat a girl with respect,
모든 일은 다 일어나게 마련이야
왜냐면 자연의 순리니까
then whatever happens is meant to happen,
because it's all perfectly natural.
얘들아
인생의 시험에 앞서
Boys, I've prepared you for this quest.
한 가지 부탁이 있단다
And before you lies
the biggest test of your lives.
이 책은 강력한
무기니까
This book is a powerful weapon,
나쁜 용도로 쓰지 말고
so use it for good,
지혜롭게 쓰렴
not evil.
네
Yes.
(SIGHS)
(DOOR CLOSING)
청소기 찾으세요?
ROB: You still looking for the vacuum?
코디 방에서 찾았단다
정말 이상하지
No. I found it
in Cody's room. So strange.
내가 언제 뒀는지
기억이 안 난다니까
I mean, I just don't remember
leaving it there.
건망증이 오나봐
(LAUGHS) Losing my mind, clearly.
엄마 저 스키 여행
가도 되요?
Hey, Mom, can I
go on the ski trip?
그래
Yes.
그 대신 술은 마시면 안돼
또 술 마셨으면 운전하지 말고
But no drinking,
and if you do drink, no driving.
걱정마세요
제가 나쁜 짓하면
유튜브에 뜰 거예요
Don't worry. If I do anything wrong,
I'm sure it'll end up on YouTube, so...
도착하면
전화할 게요
Call you when I get there.
(CHATTERING)
(ALL WHOOPING)
한 바퀴 더 돌자
Drinking round!
-나도 낄래
-여기서 뭐 해?
- Deal me in.
- What are you doing here?
난 케이티야
Katie.
나도 알아
너 여기서 뭐 해?
I know. But what are you doing here?
-나도 놀고 싶어서
-알았어
- I wanna play.
- Right.
스티플러 그냥 끼워 줘
상관없잖아
Just deal her in, Stifler.
What's the big deal?
그래 끼워 줘
AMY: Yeah, deal her in.
안녕 네이슨
Hi, Nathan.
꽃 정말 고마워
Thanks for the flowers.
멍청이처럼 굴어서 미안해
이제 뭔가 교훈을 얻었어
I'm sorry about being a jerk.
And, for the record, I've learned my lesson.
널 존중할 준비가 되었어
네 서약을 따를 게
I'm ready to respect you
and support you on your pledge.
정말?
하지만 왜?
Really? But why?
널 위해서
섹스때문에 그러는 건 아냐
I'm in this for you.
I'm not in it just to have sex.
사실 난 널 위해
한 거였는데
Well, I realised that
I'm in this for you,
하지만 서약이 방해가 된다면
널 위하는 게 아니잖아
and if the pledge gets in the way of that,
then how good can it really be?
우리 둘에게 서로의 관점으로
볼 수 있는 좋은 기회같아
Sounds like a good basis for the two of us
to just relax and see what happens.
나 책 샀어
Look. I bought a book.
내 생각엔
1페이지부터 시작해서
I was thinking that we could
이번 주 동안 얼마나
할 수 있는지 해보는 게
재밌을 거 같아
start on page one
and then see how far we get this weekend.
1장은 역할극이야
The first three chapters are foreplay.
와
Wow.
사실 나도 읽던
책이 있어
You know, I've actually been
reading a book, as well.
혹시 폭풍혀라고
들어봤어?
Have you ever heard of the tongue tornado?
어서 가자
Okay, let's go.
원래 재밌어야 하는데
This is supposed to be fun.
난 재밌어
This isn't fun.
우선 기다려봐
넌 지혜를 가졌잖아
Just you wait.
You possess wisdom now.
책을 믿어
Trust in the book.
그게 도대체 무슨 말이야?
내가 끈적거린다고 생각해?
I mean, what does that mean, anyway?
Do you think I'm too clingy?
아냐
물론 아냐
No. No, of course not.
포커 할 줄 알아?
Do you even know how to play poker?
나도 알아
KATIE: I know the game.
내가 지면 옷을 벗을게
And I tell you what,
if I lose, I'll take off all my clothes.
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
죽인다
AMY: Snap.
ASHLEY: Nice.
내가 지면?
And if I lose?
나한테 사과 해
You apologise to me.
-뭘 사과해? 속인 거?
-그래
- For what? Blowing you off?
- KATIE: Yes.
그걸론 부족해
내 첫경험이었어
If it's not enough,
it was my first time.
난 더 대우받을만 해
I deserve better.
(GASPS)
만약 내가 이기면
사과는 물론
But if I win,
not only do you apologise to me,
벗고 눈 속을 뛸 각오해
you gotta run through the snow naked.
(ALL CHEERING)
-좋아
-받아 들이지
- Yeah.
- It's a deal.
벗을 준비해 이쁜이
Start stripping, sweetheart.
아직 안 끝났어
It's not over yet.
운이 좋을 거 같아?
Feeling lucky?
5가 나오길 비는 게 좋을 걸
You better hope for a
five on the river, baby.
5를 가졌어!
말도 안 돼
ASHLEY: She got the five! Unbelievable.
(SCREAMING)
맙소사
Oh, my God.
-벗어
-잠깐만
- Strip.
- Hold on a second.
-벗어
- Strip.
벗어! 벗어!
ALL: (CHANTING)
Strip! Strip! Strip! Strip!
벗어! 벗어!
내가 벗길 원해?
정말?
You want me to strip?
You want some of this?
자 이제 나갈 시간이야!
It's time to get it going, baby!
(ALL CHEERING)
좋아
어서 가자
All right, let's go!
Here we go, baby.
나중에 얘기 좀 해
STIFLER: Wait, let's talk this over.
젠장
얼어 죽겠네
Shit. It's freezing out here.
사과해
Now apologise.
-미안해
-뭐가 미안해?
- I'm sorry.
- For what?
너한테 전화 안해서 미안해
I'm sorry for not calling you afterwards.
그리고 또?
And what else?
멍청이같이 굴어서
미안해 됐어?
I'm sorry for being a dick, okay?
이제 문 열어 줘
Now, open the stinking door.
오!
GIRLS: Oh!
(EXCLAIMING)
문 열어!
Open the door!
자 이제 네가 얼마나
여자애같이 우는지 말해
Now, tell everyone how you cry
like a little girl after you come.
그래 나 여자같이 운다
됐어?
I cry like a
girl after I come, okay?
나한테 너무
혹독하게 구는 거 아냐
It's a very intense experience for me.
(MOOSE BELLOWING)
911에 전화해
Call 911 .
Hey, I'll meet you at the lodge later.
산장에서 봐
Yeah, yeah, sure. Go.
응 그래
ROB: Heidi. Wait up.
하이디 기다려
Do you mind if
I ride up with you?
같이 타도 괜찮겠어?
Okay.
응
Hey. What's up?
잘 지냈어?
We...We're in the same gondola.
우리 같은 곤돌라를 타네
Yeah, look at that.
그러게
(GROANING)
Oh, God.
맙소사
I didn't sleep with Stifler.
나 스티플러랑 안 잤어
Yeah. I heard.
응 들었어
- But you still hate me?
- No.
-그래도 여전히 내가 싫어?
-아니
No. Why would you say that?
그런 건 왜 물어봐?
You haven't said a word to me
since that night.
그 날 이후로
아무 말도 안 하길래
I know. I'm sorry.
아 미안
I guess I just...
I needed time to work through my feelings.
내 감정을 정리할
시간이 필요했어
And? What did you decide?
그래서?
정리는 됐어?
Gibbs says that Stifler has to sit on
a foam rubber doughnut for six weeks.
깁스가 그러는데 스티플러는
6개월동안 도넛 모양
고무의자를 써야 한대
And he says they're talking about
amputating his feet from frostbite.
그리고 동상때문에
발을 자를지도 모른대
Gibbs is a liar.
Stifler doesn't need amputation.
깁스는 거짓말쟁이야
스티플러는 다리 안 잘라
That's too bad.
I got an A in Shop.
아쉽다
공작 시간에 A 받았는데
(SNORTS)
Oh, my. Was that a snort?
코에서 난 소리야?
Come to gloat?
고소하냐?
No. Just looking for a fag.
아니
담배 찾으러 온 거야
Just 'cause I took a moose pickle up my ass
doesn't mean I'm gay.
무스한테 당했다고
내가 게이가 된 건 아냐
Very funny. How's your bum?
재밌네
엉덩이는 어때?
Feels like I gave birth to a mayonnaise jar,
but thanks for asking.
엉덩이로 마요네즈 병을
낳은 거 같아, 물어봐줘서 고마워
Hey, I heard about your boyfriend.
That really sucks.
네 남친 얘기 들었어
안 됐더라
Yeah. I thought only high school boys
were jerks.
난 고등학교 애들만
싸가지 없는 줄 알았어
It turns out they never outgrow it.
결국 남자들은
다 똑같다는 게 밝혀졌지
Lmogen, no offence,
and you're the most mature girl I know,
나쁘게 듣지마, 이모진
넌 내가 아는 애 중 가장 성숙해
but a 24-year-old dude isn't gonna take
a high-school girl seriously.
그렇다고 24살 짜리가
고등학교 애를 진지하게
생각하진 않아
I suppose not.
난 그렇게 생각 안 해
You wanna sit down?
앉을래?
What for?
왜?
I just thought we could both use
a friend right now.
우리 둘이 지금 서로
친구가 필요한 거 같아서
Stifler.
스티플러
My bad. Reflex.
미안
반사 작용이라
(LAUGHS)
ROB: I'm sorry.
미안해
You have to make your own decisions.
너도 결정을 해야 해
You know, I just...
I thought we had something.
난 아직 우리 사이에
뭔가 있다고 생각해
We did.
그래 맞아
We do.
아직 감정이
남아 있어
I was scared.
난 무서웠어
Of what?
뭐가 무서워?
I really like you.
내가 널 너무 좋아해서
And I want it to be special.
그래서 특별했으면 좋겠어
I guess I just wanted to be ready.
내가 준비가 되기만을
기다린 거 같아
So you almost had sex with Stifler
so you'd be ready for me.
스티플러랑 거의 섹스할 뻔
했으니 네가 준비가 됐다고
생각하는 거구나
Yeah.
응
That's the dumbest thing I've ever heard.
내가 들어본 말 중
가장 바보같은 말이야
Well, I heard you got some practise.
글쎄.. 네가 연습을
했다고 들었어
You know, the truth is,
is nothing happened.
사실 아무 일도
없었어
I didn't want it
to be random like that.
그렇게 아무 하고나
하고 싶지 않았어
And...
그리고
I couldn't picture my first time
being with anybody else but you.
네가 아닌 다른 사람과의
첫경험은 안된다고 생각해
What was that?
무슨 일이지?
I don't know.
나도 모르겠어
- Looks like we're stuck.
- Yeah.
-우리 갇혔나봐
-그러게
You know, we could be
up here for a while.
뭐 잠깐
여기 있어도 되지 뭐
Yeah.
응
LUBE: Hey, can I ask you a question?
뭐 물어 봐도 돼?
Yeah, sure. Whatever.
물론이지
Why do you hook up with assholes
like Scott Stifler anyway?
왜 스티플러같은
멍청이들이랑 잤어?
Excuse me, but you don't know me.
미안하지만
넌 날 잘 모르잖아
(SCOFFS) You know,
you're just the same as all the rest.
너도 다른 애들과
똑같구나
I'm just some sort of trophy to you.
난 너한테 무슨
트로피 같겠지
You don't care about me.
You just wanna sleep with me,
넌 날 신경쓰지도 않잖아
같이 자고 싶을 뿐
because you think
it's some sort of status symbol.
왜냐면 그 게 뭔가
신분의 상징이라 생각하니까
Sorry.
미안해
(ASHLEY SIGHS)
God.
세상에
How long are we gonna be up here?
얼마 동안이나
여기 있었던 거야?
I'll get help.
내가 도움을
요청할 게
ASHLEY: What are you doing?
뭐 하는 거야?
It's not that far down,
and there's, like, 20 feet of snow.
별로 높지도 않아
눈도 20피트나 쌓여 있고 뭐
What, is this supposed to impress me?
날 감동시키려고
그러는 거야?
The thought had crossed my mind.
그 생각이 들긴 했어
Absolutely not.
First of all, it's just wrong.
절대 하지마
우선 이 건 잘못된 거야
Second of all,
you're not even supposed to touch the door.
두번째로 넌 그 문에
손대면 안 돼
And third, it's just really dangerous, okay?
So just get away from there.
세번째로 매우 위험하고 말야
그러니까 빨리 이리 와
Right. What was I thinking?
맞아
내가 무슨 생각한거지?
Whoa!
으악!
(ASHLEY SCREAMING)
Are you okay?
괜찮아?
I think I hurt my leg.
다리를 다친 거 같아
(SIGHS)
Idiot.
바보같이
Are you okay?
괜찮아?
Are you crazy?
너 미쳤어?
Are you okay?
괜찮아?
Yeah, I'm fine. No, I'm fine. I'm fine.
응 괜찮아
About what you said
about how I don't care about you
아까 네가
난 널 신경 안 쓰고
and you're just a trophy,
that's actually not true.
트로피처럼 생각한다고 했잖아
그건 사실이 아냐
I really like you.
We went to elementary school together.
난 네가 정말 좋아
우린 초등학교도 같이 나왔어
I remember when you sang Hey Ya!
In the sixth-grade talent show.
6학년 장기 자랑에서 네가
'Hey Ya!'라는 노래 부른 것도 기억해
I remember when you fell off the pyramid
at the homecoming game, freshman year.
1학년 동창회때 피라미드에서
떨어진 것도 기억해
You were so embarrassed, but I didn't care.
넌 창피해 했지만
난 상관 안 했어
I just liked how you played it off
like it was all part of the routine.
난 네가 꼭 아무 일 없었다는 듯
행동하는 게 너무 좋았어
I mean, yeah, sure, you're a super-hot babe,
but I actually like you for you.
네가 정말 섹시하고 이쁘지만
난 그냥 딱 너라서 좋은 거야
Look, this may be a shock to you,
내 말에 놀랄지 모르겠지만
but I have no idea
what I'm doing with girls.
나도 내가 여자애들한테
왜 그러는지 모르겠어
But I really wanna learn.
You just give me a chance.
나한테 기회를 줘
That's all I'm asking.
내가 원하는 건
오직 그 거 뿐이야
And I guarantee that
I will make it my life's mission
나의 인생의 목표가
너를 모든 방면에 있어서
to satisfy you in every way possible.
만족 시키는 거라고
장담할 수 있어
- Let's go back to the...
- To the cabin.
-어서 다시 돌아가자
- 그래 산장으로
Dude. You forgot to sign it.
사인하는 거 잊었어
You sure we can't just keep it
for one more year?
1년 더 가지고 있으면
안 되겠지?
No, guys, it's someone else's turn.
안 돼
이젠 다른 사람 차례야
ROB ON COMPUTER.
This is my little brother, Cody,
제 동생 코디가
and this is what he does
with the vacuum every day.
진공 청소기를
가지고 매일 하는 짓이에요
No! Hey! No!
안 돼!
COD Y: Help! It's stuck!
I can't get it off!
도와줘! 꼈어!
안 빠져!
(COD Y GRO ANING)
Help! Help!
It's stuck.
도와줘! 꼈어!
(LAUGHS) Gotcha.
꼴 좋다!
COD Y: Help!
도와줘!
No!
안 돼!
She was using me. l...
That was really bad.
절 이용했어요!
내가 생각해도 정말 못 하네
Father, why hast Thou forsaken me?
아버지 왜 절 버리셨어요?
Wanna suck me off in the Sharper lmage?
내 꺼 빨고
날씬해 지는 게 어때?
Rob, are you some kind of jive turkey?
롭 너 무슨 쓸모없는
겁쟁이야?
He's like an inch
away from the real McCoy.
1인치 부족한 진품이었어요
Did you bring condoms?
콘돔 가져왔어?
What?
뭐?
I wet the bed until
I was 13 years old, okay?
13살 때까지 침대에
오줌쌌어 됐어?
You nancy boys couldn't get lucky
at a Jonas Brothers concert
게이같은 너네는
조나스 브라더스
with a fistful of backstage passes.
콘서트 대기실 입장권
못 구할 걸
Faith in God and
His promise of eternal life.
신을 믿으면 분명
영생을 주실 겁니다
Now, put the condom on the banana.
자 바나나에 콘돔을
끼워 보렴
Who didn't see that coming?
Look at the time. Gotta go.
누가 왔는지 보게나
시간을 보니까 가야 겠어
I think that is quite enough pictures
of the cheerleaders.
치어리더 사진은
그정도면 됐어요
How about we get some of the game?
경기 사진이나
찍지 그래요?
We're eating.
밥 먹어
(FARTS)
You've been fucking Americans or...
넌 정말 형편없는
미국인 이거나 아님..
Watching, loving...
쳐다 보고
사랑해 주고
Bear with me.
참고 들어 주세요
If she's down, bring her flowers.
기분이 나쁘면
꽃을 사 주고
If she's thirsty, serve her fine champagne.
목마르다면
샴페인을 줘
Yeah, 'cause, I'm telling you,
my wife is pretty effing hot.
그래 물론 우리 마누라가
죽여주게 섹시하니깐
하는 소리야
I'm talking a tight, tight ass
and squeaky clean.
그래 마누라가
아주 구두쇠에 청순해
Is that cream-filled? You rock.
안에 크림 들은 거야?
네가 최고야
Oh. Don't mention that, okay?
오 그 말은 하지마
알았지?
And whenever it comes to making out,
put on side one of Led Zeppelin IV.
섹스하기 전에
레드 재플린 4집의 CD1을 넣어